[
    {
        "question": "dog",
        "answer": "perro",
        "answers": ["gato", "caballo", "perro"],
        "imageName": "dog"
    },
    {
        "question": "house",
        "answer": "casa",
        "answers": ["escuela", "casa", "biblioteca"],
        "imageName": "house"
    },
    {
        "question": "car",
        "answer": "coche",
        "answers": ["coche", "avión", "tren"],
        "imageName": "car"
    },
    {
        "question": "book",
        "answer": "libro",
        "answers": ["revista", "diario", "libro"],
        "imageName": "book"
    },
    {
        "question": "water",
        "answer": "agua",
        "answers": ["fuego", "agua", "tierra"],
        "imageName": "water"
    },
    {
        "question": "table",
        "answer": "mesa",
        "answers": ["mesa", "silla", "puerta"],
        "imageName": "table"
    },
    {
        "question": "chair",
        "answer": "silla",
        "answers": ["silla", "mesa", "ventana"],
        "imageName": "chair"
    },
    {
        "question": "apple",
        "answer": "manzana",
        "answers": ["plátano", "pera", "manzana"],
        "imageName": "apple"
    },
    {
        "question": "school",
        "answer": "escuela",
        "answers": ["hospital", "escuela", "tienda"],
        "imageName": "school"
    },
    {
        "question": "city",
        "answer": "ciudad",
        "answers": ["ciudad", "pueblo", "país"],
        "imageName": "city"
    }
]

